<contentList date="9/17/2023 12:27">
  <content contentuid="h4a27f775g9d8fg4cc8g8306g459441c67e79" version="1">Horizon Walker</content>
  <content contentuid="h95f46c0bg9206g4ce4g8d63gd72166856b80" version="1">Horizon walkers guard the world against threats that originate from other planes or that seek to ravage the mortal realm with otherworldly magic. They seek out planar portals and keep watch over them, venturing to the Inner Planes and the Outer Planes as needed to pursue their foes. These rangers are also friends to any forces in the multiverse – especially benevolent dragons, fey, and elementals – that work to preserve life and the order of the planes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7725f5a4gfd22g40f4gb5b9g8accedd491aa" version="1">Planar Warriors Mark Owner</content>
  <content contentuid="h8f55747ag71a8g41cbga1a3gdf1fcf616514" version="1">This creature will deal extra force damage to the marked target and convert all damage to force on its next weapon attack this turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h65b8ac57g496fg4ae8gbf9fgc8eb91690795" version="1">Planar Warriors Mark</content>
  <content contentuid="h960ac7a2gf15eg4157g8d2bg72a063f67429" version="1">This creature will receive extra force damage from the targeter and receive all damage as force damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3243be5aga8d5g490bgb3e8g9429e691bd8c" version="1">Planar Warriors Mark</content>
  <content contentuid="hdda45404gc9abg4296ga898g75b5fa199c43" version="1">Choose a creature you can see within 30 feet, your next successful weapon attack against it this turn will deal an additional [1] and all damage dealt by the attack becomes force damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd745986cg8f8dg4a8bgaef5ge595ccb47124" version="1">Planar Gate</content>
  <content contentuid="h30ff5214g89b4g4c6bg938egfd652c031a6f" version="1">Create a rift (Portal) in the fabric of the Material Plane, through the Ethereal Plane, allowing creatures to travel between two specified portal points.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf08bde24gf704g4042g83eagb263ff661586" version="1">Ethereal Step</content>
  <content contentuid="h93bdfeefg16d4g42bdg9068ge6b285016fe7" version="1">You step into the border regions of the Ethereal Plane until the end of the current turn. You are invisible to creatures on the Material Plane unless a special ability or magic has given them the ability to see you. You ignore objects and effects originating from the Material Plane.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5cf0e9acg4d18g4df7g9a34g14ec070fecba" version="1">Return To Material Plane</content>
  <content contentuid="h13552184gdf06g4ba7ga315g1b30451fd358" version="1">Leave the Ethereal Plane and return to the Material Plane.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf44f4d0dg3348g4ffbgb72fgd631485ea704" version="1">Distant Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h0aefa38eg7a29g4766g8a53g19480943f428" version="1">Distant Strike (Extra)</content>
  <content contentuid="h826f993fge2c2g4b77gaf15gfab50a2408e4" version="1">You have the ability to pass between the planes in a blink of an eye. You gain an ability, allowing you to teleport up to 10 feet to an unoccupied space you can see before an attack. If you attack at least two different creatures with the action, you can make one additional attack with it against a third creature.</content>
  <content contentuid="hebdbce6dgccadg4abag9a72g9959cf369c51" version="1">Teleport up to 10 feet away before then making a weapon attack against the targeted creature.</content>
  <content contentuid="hce1e526ag748ag40f9gab4fg4594b493d31c" version="1">Distant Strike Target</content>
  <content contentuid="he1d9e0bcg96f7g4246gbc04g6f9b078c7790" version="1">The target of a Distant Strike attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6aee6457g35f7g49b2g9841g9acbc6360c3d" version="1">Has Distant Struck Two Targets</content>
  <content contentuid="h31dc23eega76eg4ee5g9002g5299249012b8" version="1">USEME</content>
  <content contentuid="h4f746ccbg3debg4575gb10ag4ea721db4ead" version="1">USEME</content>
</contentList>